

WONG KIEN HAW

Tel: +60 12-3806396 | Email: kienhaw@1utar.my

PROFILE

Address: No.19, Jalan permaisuri 15/6

Age: 24

ABOUT ME

From 2020 to 2021, I studied for a diploma in ICT (Software Engineering) at Asia Pacific University of Technology and Innovation (APU). Currently, I am pursuing a bachelor's degree in Software Engineering at Universiti Tunku Abdul Rahman (UTAR). I gained valuable experience through a two-month internship at JustSimple (M) Sdn Bhd, where I leveraged my programming knowledge to fulfil the requirements of a software development internship.

EDUCATION

Asia Pacific University | KL, Malaysia

Oct 2020 – Dec 2022

Diploma in ICT (Software Engineering)

Key Modules: Database System, Programming with Python, Web Development & Java Programming

Universiti Tunku Abdul Rahman | KL, Malaysia

Oct 2023 - Present

Bachelor's degree in SE (Software Engineering)

Key Modules: Software Testing, Software Design, Software Project Management, Problem Solving, Wireless Applications Development, Software Construction and configuration.

PROJECTS

Airline Reservations System

- A Python programming language project Asia Pacific University Assignment Project 2021.
- Developed the functionalities of Admin for the system in Python.
- Used of Pseudocode and Flowchart in the documentation.
- Distinction in this project (Python Group Assignment).

Transportation Accessory System

- This is a Java Project built at Universiti Tunku Abdul Rahman (UTAR) 2024.
- Developed the functionalities for the system in Java.

Book Shopping App

- This is a React Native app developed using Android Studio. The development process involves JavaScript, JSON and Python built at Universiti Tunku Abdul Rahman (UTAR) 2024.
- This is a wireless application developed through Android Studio.
- Using SQLite for Database.

Online Blood Donation System

- This is a Website works with HTML, CSS, PHP, PhpMyAdmin and Java Script built at Asia Pacific University Assignment 2022
- Using SQL Server for database

Online Customer Inspection and Tracking of Delivered Goods System

- This is a Website works with HTML, CSS, PHP, PhpMyAdmin and Java Script.
- Using SQL Server for database

Spiderman Online Food Services SOFS

• This is a Java Project and using JFrame at the Online Food Ordering System

OTHER EXPERIENCE

EU YAN SANG (1959) SDN BHD | KL, Malaysia

Nov 2019 - Jan 2020

Worker

- As a porter responsible for preparing customer orders, managing inventory and replenishment
- Learn teamwork, communication skills, management skills and business processes.

JustSimple (M) Sdn Bhd | Damansara, Malaysia

Oct 2020 - Dec 2022

Internship

- As an intern, learned to use WordPress, AJAX, JavaScript and CSS.
- complete a backend system independently
- know how to communicate with others.

SKILLS

- Strong leadership within group environments
- Ability to work in an organized and timely manner
- Strong interpersonal and cross-team collaboration skills
- Problem-solving skills with programming
- Excellent written and verbal communication skills
- Highly organized and efficient
- Ability to work independently or as part of a team
- Proven leadership skills and ability to motivate
- Effective communication with others

TECHNICAL SKILLS

- Hardware troubleshooting
- Network troubleshooting

- Programming (Java, C++, Visual Basic, Android Programming Language, Python, HTML, CSS, PHP, JavaScript, SQL)
- Github, Cisco Packet Tracer
- Microsoft Office (MS Word, Excel, Powerpoint)

LANGUAGES

- Chinese (Native)
- English (Basic communication)
- Malay (Basic communication)

CERTIFICATIONS

• CCNAv7: Introduction to Networks (Certificate of Course Completion)
Cisco Networking Academy, 8 May 2022